olsen-twins-news.com 2010-12-12

# Olsen Twins NEWS Privacy Statement

## Privacy

**Third Party Advertising  
**We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here [Networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp)

**Olsen Twins News Respects Your Privacy**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Olsen Twins News.

**External Sites**

Olsen Twins News is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on the sites you visit on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Cookies**

A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Olsen Twins News to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Olsen Twins News does not use cookies to collect personal information. 

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Olsen Twins News and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Olsen Twins News have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. 

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information use the contact form [here](http://www.olsen-twins-news.com/contact-me/)
